Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series A: Arts
  - Subseries 3: Judson Poet's Theater
    - Judson Poets' Theater-In Circles/Big Projects, I Suppose 10/6/1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Sing Ho for a Bear! Dec. 13-21, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Untitled Play/The Sayings of Mao Tse-Tung 1/26/1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Celebration/The Sayings of Mao Tse-Tung 2/5/1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Line of Least Existence 3/15/, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Doctor Kheal /Do Not Go Gentle/The Making 3/3/, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Aristophanes' Peace 11/1/1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Arenas of Lutetia 11/22/1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Poor Little Match Girl 12/22/1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Closer Since the Shooting 2/8/1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Future March-April 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Mid-Kingdom of Lions May 16-19, 23-26, 30-31, June 1-2, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Chinese Dancer/A Rehearsal/The 11th Dynasty June 20-23, 27-30, July 4-7, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Urban Crisis 10/29/1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Judson Poets' Theater/Dance Theater-Three Women/Dracula 11/1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings 12/14/1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Manitoba/Little Burgundy Feb. 20-24, 27-28, Mar. 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-About Time Apr. 12-13, 17-20, 24-27, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Dracula: Sabbat Sept. 11-14, 18-21, 25-28, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Playful Tyrant Oct. 18- 19, 23-26, 30-31, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 13-23, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Three Plays by Lyon Phelps Feb. 18- 19, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Journey of Snow White Feb. 26-28, Mar. 1, 5-7, 12-14, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Sand Castle/Royal Flesh June 7-13, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Soundworks, Weed To Woman (a benefit for Judson) July 9-10, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Wanted Sept. 17-20, 24-25, 27, Oct. 1-4, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Joan Nov. 19-23, 26-30, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 17-23, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-A Look at the Fifties Apr. 14-18, 21-25, 28-29, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Life of a Man Sept. 29-30, Oct. 1-2, 6-9, 13-16, 20-23, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Making of Americans Nov. 10-13, 17-20, 24-27, Dec. 1-4, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 15-23, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Faggot Apr. 13-16, 20-23, 27-30, May 4-7, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Religion Oct. 26-29, Nov. 2-5, 9-12, 16-19, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 14-18, 21-23, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Financial Figures 1974- 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Future Mar. 22-25, 29-31, Apr. 1, 5-8, 12-15, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Listen to Me Oct. 11-14, 18-21, 25-28, Nov. 1-4, 22-25, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas '74 Dec. 18-22, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Sacred and Profound Love 2/28, Mar. 1-3, 7-10, 14-17, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Journey of Snow White Mar. 29-30, June 1-2, 5-9, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Why I Love New York Oct. 10-13, 17-20, 24-27, 31, Nov. 1-3, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 12-15, 18-22, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Three Evenings on a Revolving Stage Jan. 8-10, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Bonus Army Feb. 20-22, 26-29, Mar. 4-7, 11-14, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Camp Meeting May 20-24, 27-31, June 3-7, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Beast: A Meditation on Beauty Nov. 5-8, 12-15, 19-22, 26-29, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 9-13, 16-20, 22-23, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-A Manoir Apr. 22-25, 29-30, May 1-2, 6-9, 20-23, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Camp Meeting Aug. 5-8, 12-15, 19-22, 26-29, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Carmines at the Ballroom Aug. 30-Sept. 3, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Chant A Capella Nov. 18-20, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 15-19, 20-21, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Newman Retrospective-Five Films by Robert Newman 3/8/1978 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Tatyana Repina Mar. 31, Apr. 1-3, 7-10, 14-17, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-In Praise of Death Nov. 3-6, 8-13, 17-20, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 14-17, 19-21, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-A Summer Bouquet of Old Songs (Carmines and Vaughan 9th annual benefit) June 16-17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Someone's In the Kitchen with Dinah July 27-30, Aug. 3-6, 10-13, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights [see oversize] Oct. 26-29, Nov. 2-5, 9-12, 16-19, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 12-15, 18-20, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-A Nosegay of Old Songs (Carmines/Vaughan) May 25-26, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Agony of Paul Oct. 3-6, 10-13, 17-20, 24-27, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Christmas Rappings Dec. 12-15, 18-22, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-T. S. Eliot: Midwinter Vigilante March, 20-23, 27-30, Apr. 3-6, 10-13, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Tragedy of Salome (Stanford Group) Oct. 7-10, 14-17, 21-24, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Rundown (Bob Auletta-The Private Theater Company) Jan. 13-16, 19-23, 26-30, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Death of Edgar Allen Poe Feb. 27-28, Mar. 1-2, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Hrotswithae Opera-Callimachus, Abraham, Sapienta (Stanford Group) Apr. 3-4, 10-11, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-The Tale of Plagues and Carnivals (Delany and Wise) 6/25/1987 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Working Theater-Heroes and Saints Nov. 30-Jan. 1, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-Queer Theater (conference hosted by Judson Church) Apr. 27-29, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Judson Poets' Theater-25 Years Since Kent State 5/4/1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Reviews-About Time, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Reviews-The Agony of Paul, 10/1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Reviews-Antigone/Red Cross, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Reviews-Asphodel, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Reviews-An Audio-Visual/La Luz/Black Traveler/Revenge on Little Orphan Annie, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Reviews-The Beast: A Meditation on Beauty, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Reviews-A Beautiful Day/Play I, Play II, Play III, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Reviews-The Birthday, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Reviews-A Birthday Tribute to Irving Berlin, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Reviews-The Bitch of Waverly Place, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Reviews-Black Traveler/La Luz/An Audio-Visual/Revenge on Little Orphan Annie, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Reviews-The Bonus Army, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Reviews-The Beast of Tiresias, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Reviews-Trisha Brown, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Reviews-Camp Meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Reviews-Carmines at the Ballroom, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Reviews-Central Park Bench No. 33, Flight 207, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Reviews-Chant A Capella 11/1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1969 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1971 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1975 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1977 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Reviews-Christmas Rappings 1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Reviews-The Decapitated Taxi/The War Engine, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Reviews-Devices, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Reviews-The Devil's Mother/Malcauchon, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Reviews-Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Reviews-Dr. Kheal, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Reviews-Dracula: Sabbat, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Reviews-The Executives, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Reviews-The Faggot, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Reviews-For Madeleine Renaud, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Reviews-The Future, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Reviews-God is My Ram/Miss Right, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Reviews-Gorilla Queen, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Reviews-The Great American Desert, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Reviews-Hagar and Ishmael, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Reviews-Harmony, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Reviews-Hector the Heroic, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Reviews-Home Movies, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Reviews-The Hundred and First, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Reviews-Hurrah It's Lewis Carroll Day, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Reviews-The In Out, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Reviews-In Praise of Death, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Reviews-Inroads Rebuffed, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Reviews-Istanbul, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Reviews-Joan, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Reviews-Jourmard/Women at the Tomb, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Reviews-The Journey of Snow White 1971 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Reviews-The Journey of Snow White 1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Reviews-Leonce and Lena/Patter for a Soft Shoe, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Reviews-Lesson in Understanding, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Reviews-The Life of a Man, undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Reviews-The Line of Least Existence, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Reviews-Listen to Me, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Reviews-Katherine Litz Dance Company, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Reviews-A Look at the Fifties, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Reviews-The Love Cure/The Tightrope Walker, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Reviews-La Luz/An Audio-Visual/Black Traveler/Revenge on Little Orphan Annie, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Reviews-The Making of Americans, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Reviews-Malcauchon/The Devil's Mother, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Reviews-A Manoir, undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Reviews-Mask of Angels, undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Reviews-Miss Right/God Is My Ram, undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Reviews-The Monster, undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Reviews-Murder Cake, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Reviews-The Nativity Plays of the York Mysteries, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Reviews-Nice Place You Got Here, undated (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Reviews-The Old Tune, undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Reviews-Pantaleize, undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Reviews-Patter for a Soft Shoe/Leonce and Lena, undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Reviews-Peace, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Reviews-The Pelican, undated (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Reviews-Perez, Rudy/Men's Coalition, undated (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Reviews-Playful Tyrant, undated (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Reviews-Pomegranada, undated (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Reviews-The Private Potato Patch of Greta Garbo, undated (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Reviews-Promenade, undated (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Reviews-Red Cross/Antigone, undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Reviews-Religion, undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Reviews-The Reservation, undated (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Reviews-Revenge on Little Orphan Annie/An Audio-Visual/La Luz/Black Traveler, undated (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Reviews-Romantic and Animal Meditations, undated (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Reviews-Sacred and Profane Love, undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Reviews-San Francisco Burning, undated (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Reviews-The Sayings of Mao Tse-Tung/Untitled Play, undated (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Reviews-Sightseer, undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Reviews-Sing Ho for a Bear!, undated (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Reviews-Softly, and Consider the Nearness, undated (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Reviews-Someone's in the Kitchen with Dinah, undated (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Reviews-Song of Songs, undated (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Reviews-The String Game, undated (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Reviews-T. S. Eliot: Midwinter Vigil (ante), undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Reviews-Tatyana Repina, undated (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Reviews-Three Sisters Who Are Not Sisters, undated (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Reviews-Three Thousand Ants, undated (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Reviews-The Tightrope Walker/The Love Cure, undated (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Reviews-Untitled Play/The Sayings of Mao Tse-Tung, undated (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Reviews-The Urban Crisis, undated (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Reviews-Vaudeville Skit, undated (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Reviews-Vaughan/Carmines Concert 1975 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Reviews-Wagoner, Dan and Dancers, undated (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Reviews-Wanted, undated (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Reviews-Waring, James Festival, undated (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Reviews-The Wax Engine/The Decapitated Taxi, undated (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Reviews-What Happened?, undated (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Reviews-Why I Love New York, undated (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Reviews-Women at the Tomb/Jourmard, undated (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Reviews-You're As Old As Your Arteries, undated (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Scripts-Oppenheimer, Joel. The Great American Desert 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Scripts-The Second Shepherd's Play (2 of 3 scenes) 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Scripts-Anderson, C. V. J. The Executives 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Scripts-Dennison, George. The Service for Joseph Axminster 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Scripts-Goodman, Paul. The Birthday (production) 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Scripts-Goodman, Paul. Hagar and Ishmael 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Scripts-The New York Nativity Mysteries 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Scripts-Oppenheimer/Carmines. Miss Right 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Scripts-Susac, Andrew. God Is My Ram 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Scripts-Dennison, G. Patter for a Soft-Shoe Dance 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Scripts-DiPrima, Diane. Poet's Vaudeville 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Scripts-Katzman, Dan. Harrah! It's Lewis Carroll Day 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Scripts-Sainer, Arthur. The Bitch of Waverley Place 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude. What Happened? Music by Al Carmines 1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Scripts-Wieners, John. Asphodel 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Scripts-Brecht, Bertold. A Lesson in Understanding 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Scripts-Brown, Kenneth. Devices 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Scripts-Cameron, Kenneth. The Hundred and First 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Scripts-Dennison, George. Harmony [see oversize] 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Scripts-Falcone, Richard. Nice Place You Got Here 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Scripts-LaBar, T. Sightseer 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Scripts-Owens, Rochelle. The String Game 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Scripts-Prada, Cecilia. Central Park Bench 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude. Three Sisters Who Were Not Sisters 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Thanksgiving Cantata for the City (worship service) 1965 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Scripts-Falcone, R. The Monster 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene. The Promenade (original submitted script) 1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene. The Promenade (before revisions) 1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene. The Promenade 1966 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Scripts-Haut, Howard. Revenge on Little Orphan Annie 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Scripts-Kenemy, Alex. You're As Old As Your Arteries 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Scripts-Kenemy, Alex. You're As Old As Your Arteries 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Scripts-Koutoukas, H. M. Pomegranada 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Scripts-Krauss, Ruth. A Beautiful Day (Seven Poem Plays) 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Scripts-Marz, Roy. After Closing 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Scripts-Owens, Rochelle. Istanboul 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Scripts-Shephard, Sam. Red Cross 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude. Play I, Play II, Play III 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Scripts-Sullivan, J. Roy. The Private Potato Patch of Greta Garbo 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Scripts-Zalk, Mark. Hector the Heroic! 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Scripts-Zalk, Mark. Hector the Heroic! 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Scripts-Adam, Helen and Pat. San Francisco's Burning (bound script) (1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Scripts-Adam, Helen/Al Carmines. San Francisco's Burning 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Scripts-Adam, Helen/Al Carmines. San Francisco's Burning 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene. The Successful Life of 3 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene. The Successful Life of 3 (production scripts) 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Scripts-Fornes, Maria Irene.1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Scripts-Kenan, Amos. The Lion1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Scripts-Lee, Maryat. The Tightrope Walker 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Scripts-Sing Ho for a Bear! (Winnie the Pooh) stories by A. A. Milne, adapted by Robert Sargent and Lawrence Kornfield, music by Al Carmines 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Scripts-Sing Ho for a Bear-pieces (incomplete?) 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Scripts-Sing Ho for a Bear-script cards 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Scripts-Sing Ho for a Bear-first draft 1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Scripts-Moliere. The Love Cure-trans. By John Wood 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Scripts-Nichols, B. Scene from a Street Play (includes director's copy) 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Scripts-Portnoy, Edward. Folie a Deux 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Scripts-Solanas, Valerie. Scum Manifesto (1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Scripts-Tavel, Ronald. Gorilla Queen-stage manager's book 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Scripts-Tavel, Ronald Gorilla Queen 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Scripts-Adam, Helen. "Miss Laura" (poem inscribed to Al Carmines) 4/1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude/Al Carmines. In Circles 10/1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Thanksgiving Cantata 1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Scripts-Drexler, Rosalyn. The Line of Least Existence 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Scripts-Upton, Robert. Do Not Go Gentle 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Scripts-Kenemy, Alex. Big Projects, I Suppose 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Scripts-Wilson, Lanford. Untitled Play (Al's copy included)1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Scripts-Aristophanes. Peace (trans. by Tim Reynolds) 11/1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Scripts-Faber, Robert Mason. Mid-Kingdom of Lions 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Scripts-Williams, Arthur/Al Carmines. The Poor Little Match Girl 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Scripts-Barnes, Theo/Al Carmines About Time 4/1970 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Scripts-Gauthier, Guy. Little Burgundy 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Scripts-Gauthier, Guy. Manitoba 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Scripts-Metzger, Wendell. The Eleventh Dynasty 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Scripts-Nichols, Robert. Riot and the Famous Fire 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Scripts-Katz, Leon. Dracula: Sabbat 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Scripts-Phelps, Lyon. Four Actors and a Restaurant 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Joan 11/1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. A Look at the Fifties 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted (partial manuscript and financial information) 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted (Arthur Zinberg's copy) 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted (David Epstein's copy) 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines Wanted (Al Carmines' working copy) 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude. The Making of Americans-opera and play by Leon Katz 11-12/1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. The Faggot 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. The Faggot (scripts, working parts and music) 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. The Future 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude/Al Carmines. Listen to Me 10-11/1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude/Al Carmines. Listen to Me 10-11/1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines. The Bonus Army (original script) 2-3/1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines. The Bonus Army 2-3/1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Scripts-Epstein, David/Al Carmines. The Bonus Army (script parts, music, etc) 2-3- 1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Camp Meeting (original Notes, script) 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Camp Meeting 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Camp Meeting (personal copy of stage manager, Bob LoBianco, with his notes) 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. The Beast: A Meditation on Beauty (music, cast list, script, notes) 11/1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude/Al Carmines. A Manoir (three versions) 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Scripts-Stein, Gertrude/Al Carmines. A Manoir (scripts, music, contact sheet) 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Scripts-Chekhov, Anton. Tatyana Repina 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Christmas Rappings (production book) 1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Scripts-Carmines, Al. Christmas Rappings (Alleluia cheat sheets, script for David Tice) 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)